This solution appears to have a lot of potential.

Dickens, Oppenheim, London, Austen, Alcott, and Lewis are identified correctly.
Достоевский, Joyce, Twain and Voltaire are not.  Instead they are incorrectly mapped to Dickens or Austen.  In the case of the Russian author and the French author, this would be easily explained by the translator's hand in the matter.  For Joyce and Twain, there must be a more interesting explanation.  Joyce had a wide range of styles over his lifetime (compare Dubliners to Finnegans Wake, for example).  Twain may have worked hard to make the Prince and Pauper (Mystery File #10) more English-sounding, which put it in the Dickens/Austen zone.